Finding Aid for the June Wayne Papers LSC.0562
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Correspondence, 1942-1997
  - Subseries 9: Personal, 1941-2009
    - Lowry, MacNeil Estate Correspondence 1964-1993, 1964, 1973, 1980-1981, 1982-1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Biography of W. McNeil Lowry; (ca. 1980); airing of KCET television show on "The Dorothy Series"; Wayne's and Lowry's reactions to chapter in Clinton Adams' book, "American Lithographers, 1900-1960"; Tatanya Grossman obituary by Calvin Tomkins; Wayne's continuing litigation re insurance, Terry Sanders, and legal firm of Ball Hunt; New Yorker magazine (1983 September 12) containing article, "Conversations with Balanchine" by MacNeil Lowry; program for the 67th American Assembly, "The Arts and Public Policy in the United States" (Arden House, New York, 1984 May 31-June 3); establishment of search committee for director of Tamarind Institute at University of New Mexico, and Marge Devon as candidate; taping project with Sid Koch.
    - Freeman, Vera 1985-1990 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Christmas cards from Vera Freeman (Andrews/Nelson/Whitehead, New York); Vera's retirement (1986 July); Andrews/Nelson/Whitehead booklet of Japanese paper samples; Wayne's continuing litigation; Wayne's exhibitions at the Fresno Art Museum and the Associated American Artists, New York (1988); Wayne's participation in Otto Piene's "Sky Works" performance; Wayne's participation in National Print Symposium (Canberra, Australia), w/ exhibitions of her work in Sydney, Canberra and Melbourne.
    - Bird, Rose Elizabeth (Chief Justice), 1981 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Articles on California Chief Justice Rose Elizabeth Bird; letter from Chief Justice Bird re meeting Wayne at the Women's Trusteeship (Los Angeles); copy of Chief Justice Bird's remarks, "State of the Judiciary Address," given at the State Bar Conference of Delegates (San Diego.)
    - Arnold, Anna Bing & Aerol, 1958,1981-1987 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Aerol Arnold re Wayne's exhibition in San Francisco; Anna Bing Arnold re her accident and convalescence; illness and death of Aerol Arnold; photograph of Aerol Arnold (1982); Wayne's comments about the Whitney Museum of American Art catalogue by Judith Goldman, "American Prints: Process & Proofs"; Wayne's exhibition of paintings at the Armstrong Gallery (New York, 1984); Anna's resignation from the Board of the Los Angeles County Museum of Art (LACMA); various dinner invitations.
    - Veillard, Roger & Anita; Wright, Richard, 1943, 1983, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Roger and Anita Veillard re Wayne's participation in the Salon de Mai (Paris, 1983 and 1985); Richard Wright re manuscript for story submitted by Wayne [née Claire.]
    - Segalen, Yvon, Anna & Yo, 19821983, 1985-1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Yo Segalen re illness and death of Madeleine Jarry (1982); Wayne's visit to Paris for her print exhibition at Galerie des Femmes (1985 April); Christiane Picard re illness and death of Yo Segalen; Anne Segalen (granddaughter of Victor Segalen) re her daughter, Chine Lauzmann, attending the University of Southern California (USC); Bulletins de l'Association Victor Segalen (No. 1, 1988 October; No. 3, 1989 July.)
    - Hayman, D'Arcy, 1979-1994, no date (Box 6, Folder 4)
      d'Arcy Sanger Hayman (artist, teacher, poet; Director, International Arts Program, UNESCO); copy of her book, "Embrace Me Universe and More", inscribed by the author to Wayne; various illustrated dinner invitations, including an evening with King Vidor and Samantha Eggar; Hayman's poetry and art work; death of her mother (1986 February); obituary (1994 July.)
    - Hanson, Elizabeth (Liz), 1982-1984, 1988-1989, 1991, no date (Box 7, Folder 11)
      Elizabeth Gibbons-Hanson re: Vicky Wilson (Alfred A. Knoph) re efforts to publish Hanson's "Rags" manuscript (1983); Frederic "Fritz" S. Marquardt (senior editor, Arizona Republic) re meeting Wayne (via Hanson); Hanson's surgery (1983); Hanson's move to Auburn, Alabama (1989); change of address announcement w/ photograph.
    - Greene, Henry, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      Re Greene's poetry and group, "Creative Circle"; June Rachuy Brindel's book, "Ariadne."
    - Malarcher, Patricia, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      Thank you note for visit to Wayne's studio; "Art Materialized" exhibition catalogue's mention of Tamarind.
    - Ussachevsky, Vladimir (Betty), 1941, 1985, 1988-1990, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      Correspondents include: Vladimir Ussachevsky's re collected letters of his wife, Elizabeth (Betty) Kray; programs for Elizabeth Kray memorial service (1987 November 25, Cathedral of St. John the Divine, New York); copy of "Chelsea 1904-1913: John Sloan's Neighborhood and Neighbors" by Elizabeth Kray for the Poetry Society of America (1985); Leni Spencer re Vladimir's illness, death, and memorial service; Karl Hereim (A&R administrator, New World Records, New York) re using Wayne's art work on cover of Ussachevsky album.
    - Ussachevsky, Vladimir, 1983, 1985, 1987-1989 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      Correspondents include: Betty Kray re her illness; trip to Snowbird, Utah (1987 July); Vladimir re Betty's death; also included are Betty Kray's New York Times obituary and "Elizabeth Kray 1916-1987: A Remembrance" (1988 April 9, Little Church Around the Corner, New York.)
    - Elliott, Carol, 1981-1983, 1985, 1986, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      Correspondents include: Carol Elliott's "Aesthetic Statement" about Marcia Durrant (1981 November); death of Marcia Durrant; Graduate School for Community Development (San Diego, CA) invitation to Marcia A. Durrant exhibition, "Retrospective" (1981 November 7-28, Gallery of the Multicultural Arts Institute, San Diego); Carol Elliott and William L. Shroyer (national marketing manager, Fred A. Wilson Company) re roof problems in Wayne's building; 35mm color negatives and seven 3 x 5" photos of Wayne's roof; Sandra Martinez (friend of Carol Elliott) re copy of court decision on Wayne's litigation w/ Terry Sanders over film, "Four Stones for Kaneitsu."
    - Nevelson, Louise, 1963, 1980-1986, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      Torn-off signatures from Louise Nevelson prints (offered as proof of destruction) given to Tamarind staff members or printers (destroyed, 1963); New York Times article on Nevelson in her studio (1980 April 27); invitation to preview of Diana MacKnown exhibition, "Louise Nevelson: A Photographic Essay" (1981 January 7, William A. Farnsworth Library and Art Museum, Rockland, ME); Wayne re "Dorothy Series" opening at the Jewish Museum (1981 January 9, New York); Laurie Lisle re her biography on Louise Nevelson; Wayne's opening at Armstrong Gallery (1984 October 17, New York); Wayne's appearance in Picasso play, "Catch Desire by the Tail" at the Guggenheim Museum (1984 October 25, 26); Nevelson's 85th birthday dinner given by Barbaralee and Carl Spielvogel (1984 October 17, New York); invitation to unveiling of Nevelson's sculpture, "Night Sail" (1985 June 20, Crocker Center, Los Angeles); Wayne's speech given at Hofstra Museum, Hofstra University Conference on The Avant-garde in Literature and Art (1985 November, Long Island); invitation to Nevelson's benefit show, "Wood Sculptures and Collages" for Louise Nevelson Laboratory for Cancer Immunobiology (1980 May 1, Wildenstein, New York); Nevelson exposition at Galerie Claude Bernard (1986 January 23- February 22, Paris); Grace Glueck article, "Friends of Louise Nevelson Gather in a Memorial for the Late Artist" (New York Times, 1988 October 18); thank you to Wayne from Arnold B. Glimcher (Pace Gallery, New York) for "Goodbye Louisie" lithograph; thank you from Mike Nevelson (Louise's son) re Wayne's print; invitation to "An Hour of Song: In Remembrance of Louise Nevelson" w/ Edward Albee, Jessye Norman, and James Levine (1989 March 28, Carnegie Hall.)
    - Nevelson, Louise, 1963, 1988, 1989, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      Photographs of Nevelson working in Tamarind studio (1963); articles re Nevelson's death, memorial, and estate dispute between Nevelson's assistant, Diana MacKown and son, Myron (Mike) Nevelson.
    - Nevelson, Louise, 1989, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      Dorothy Rabinowitz article "The Art of the Feud: Sculptor Louise Nevelson's Tangled Legal Legacy" in New York magazine (1989 September 25); Sharon Timmer re estate sale of Lillian Berliawsky (sister-in-law of Louise Nevelson) w/ two Nevelson paintings offered for sale (Gamage/Veilleux auction, 1993 July 10, Rockland, ME.)
    - Treiman, Joyce, 1983, 1986, 1988, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      Brochure for Treiman exhibition of paintings at Tortue Gallery, Santa Monica (1983 November 16-December 31); exhibitions announcement, "Joyce Treiman: Recent Painting and Drawings" (Tortue Gallery, 1986 November 22-December 27) and "Joyce Treiman: Recent Works" (Schmidt - Bingham Gallery, New York, 1988 April 27-May 21); Tortue Gallery's artist biography; Los Angeles Times obituary (1991 June 4); "Artist of the Area" article on Treiman (1970 December/January); Introduction and autobiography from exhibition, "Impetus: The Creative Process" (Los Angeles Municipal Art Gallery, Barnsdall Park, 1975 October 29-November 30); letter to Ruth Fine (Curator, National Gallery of Art, Washington D.C.) re possibly acquiring some of Treiman's work; documents re memorial service, "A Celebration of the Art and Life of Joyce Treiman (UCLA Dickson Art Center, 1991 June 30.)
    - Treiman, Joyce, 1970, 1984, 1988, 1990-1992 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      Exhibition catalog, "Joyce Treiman: Friends and Strangers" (Fisher Gallery, University of Southern California, 1988 January 20-February 27); "Images & Issues: Contemporary Art Review" (1984 March/April) with article by Isabel Anderson on Joyce Treiman; Tortue Gallery receipt for Wayne's purchase of Treiman's "Incident Series" (1988 January 26); letter to Treiman from Joyce re Giverny artist program and executing portraits of one another; brochure from Schmidt - Bingham Gallery (1991, New York); exhibitions, "Joyce Treiman: The Last Paintings" at Tortue Gallery, Santa Monica (1992 February 15-March 28), "Echoes: Recent Pastel Drawings", Schmidt - Bingham Gallery (1992 January 22-25, New York.)
    - Kanemitsu, Mike, 1992-1995 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      Tributes and memorial essays for the American painter, Matsumi (Mike) Kanemitsu (1922-1992) from: Conner Everts, Luchita Hurtado, Patia Rosenberg, Mac McCloud, Felix Ruvolo, Ernest T. Nagamatsu, Gerald Nordland, Ynez Johnston and John Berry, Ed Hamilton, and Katsuhisa Sakai; Wayne to Burt Folkart and Bill Wilson (Los Angeles Times) re Gerald Nordland article on Kanemitsu; notes on memorial program; exhibition announcement for "Matsumi Kanemitsu: A Retrospective" (Louis Newman Galleries, 14 - 28 January 1993, Beverly Hills, CA); Mike Kanemitsu appeared in Wayne's film, "Four Stones for Kanemitsu."
    - Kanemitsu, Mike, 1995, 1996, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Receipts from Wayne's trip to Japan (1998 February 10-17) to attend opening of Matsumi (Mike) Kanemitsu's retrospective exhibition at National Museum of Art in Osaka (1998 February 12); program plan for exhibition opening; correspondents include: Gary Lang; Kyoko "Michi" Michishita; Marjorie Devon (Director, Tamarind Institute); Akira Kurosaki (printmaker and instructor, College of Fine Arts, Kyoto Seika University); To Ko Muto; Koken Murata, including his catalogue, "Urushi" (Yamaki Art Gallery, Osaka, 1996); exhibition announcement for "Matsumi Kanemitsu (1922-1992): Works on Paper" (1995 May 13-31, Gallery IV, Los Angeles, CA)
    - Kanemitsu, Mike, 1978 Dec. 26 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      Typed transcription of Wayne's interview with Matsumi (Mike) Kanemitsu in her studio, 1978 December 26 (136 pages.)
    - Kanemitsu, Mike, 1979, 1984-1986, 1988, 1990, 1992, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      Los Angeles Times obituary for Kanemitsu (1992 May 14); correspondents include: Matsumi (Mike) Kanemitsu; Carla Luna (Louis Newman Galleries, Beverly Hills, CA) re Kanemitsu's exhibition, "California Visions: Selected Paintings 1976 - 1984" (1984 June 15-30); "Kanemitsu" exhibition brochure (1986 January 16-February 6); various exhibition announcements (1979-1990); Masatoshi Honda (Hiroshima City Museum of Contemporary Art) re Wayne presentation; Nancy Uyemura; Gerald Nordland re Paul Jenkins' letter.
    - Koch, Sig, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      Sigmund Koch (Professor of Psychology and Philosophy; Director, The Aesthetics Research Archive at Boston University) re proposal for taping interview with June Wayne.
    - RO Miscellaneous, 1981, 1982, 1984, 1986-1990, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Correspondents include: Stephen F. Rohde (attorney) to Rachel Rosenthal re his article, "Art of the State: Congressional Censorship of the National Endowment for the Arts"; David Rose; Joyce Rosenberg; Marilyn Rosenberg (Marisa Del Re Gallery, New York); Patia Rosenberg; Barry Rosengrant (President, Metrospace Corporation, Los Angeles); Tony and Halina Rosenthal (includes pamphlet for Rosenthal exhibition, Galerie Denise René, Paris, 1988 March 3-April 12); Kenneth Ross, with clipping of review of Matsumi Kanemitsu's exhibition at Louis Newman Gallery, Beverly Hills, CA); Ross Associates Speakers Bureau (Pauline Buck, Vice President) re Wayne speaking engagements.
    - Wachs, Joel, 1988, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      Joel Wachs (Councilman, 2nd district, Los Angeles City Council) re: Wayne's endorsement for Claire Isaacs; Wach's Art Table presentation at Koplin Gallery (1988); Lee Ramer (assistant to councilman Wachs); biographical sketch of Wachs (1995.)
    - WA Miscellaneous Continued: Washington Artist; (Eastern) Washington State Historical Society; Watanabe, Yoko; Watts, Towers, 1981, 1982, 1984, 1986, 1988, 1994, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      Correspondents include: Dorothy Waage re death of her husband Tom, and Wayne's show at Jewish Museum, New York; Di Waite (executive director, Print Council of Australia Inc., Melbourne) re imprint of Anne Kirker's interview with Wayne; Washington Artists (Bill Roseberry, co-chair) re reprinting Wayne's article, "The Male Artists as a Stereotypical Female"; Yoko Watanabe re critique of exhibition of Wayne's prints at Downey Museum; Jeanne Morgan re Watts Towers (includes 3x5 inch color photograph); Henry Waxman (Congressman, U.S. House of Representatives) re articles on his work; George Wayne; Kyra Wayne re property tax on Hermosa Beach property and moving to Fresno.
    - RI Miscellaneous, 1979, 1983-1988, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      Correspondents include: Bobbi and Stan Rice; Katherine T. Brown (professor of art history, Rice University, Houston, TX) re evaluation of Karin Broker for promotion; Alan Rich re Newsweek; Anne Richards (Governor of Texas); Diana Rico (freelance journalist); Bonnie Riesdesel (art student, South Dakota State University) re questionnaire; Deborah Johnson (Museum of Art, Rhode Island School of Design, i.e. RISD); Naomi S. Risdon; Elisavietta Ritchie (Wineberry Press, Washington D.C.) re her poems
    - WOL Miscellaneous: Wolf Point Productions; Wolf, Theodore; Wolf, Andrew, 1974, 1993-1994, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      Correspondents include: Andrew Ian Wolf (President, Pacific Design Center, Los Angeles.)
    - WON Miscellaneous, 1981, 1983-1985, 1988, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      Correspondents include: David Wong (apartment owner) re landscaping problems adjacent to Wayne's property on Tamarind; Yen Lu Wong (dancer, choreographer; director, The New Repertory, later known as "TNR" theater company.)
    - Reeves, Nancy, 1969-1970, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      Copy of Reeves' "Anatomy and Destiny" from Annals of the New York Academy of Sciences, vol. 175, article 3, 1970 October 30; "Stereotypes of Woman's Place" course readings, University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA, Reeves' copyright 1969; includes references and bibliography); conference proceedings "Female Studies V" from "Women and Education: The Conference as Catalyst" held 1971 November 5-7, at the University of Pittsburgh.
    - Reeves, Nancy, 1975-1977, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      Nancy Reeves re: her travel itineraries; articles and biographical summary; proposal for an International Women's Institute; brochure and Wayne's nomination form for The Wonderwoman Foundation Awards 1982; photocopies of two articles by Nancy Reeves: "Alas Chief Davis, You're Blinded by the Sunrises" (Los Angeles Times, 1975 August 14) and "Equal rights: Some notes on stereotypes" (unidentified faculty publication, University of Southern California, 1982 January 25.)
    - Reeves, Nancy, 1984-1985, 1987, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      Nancy Reeves, J.D. (Director, Center for the Study of Change, International College, Los Angeles) re her writings, concept for making a film, remarks by Wayne on Reeves' honorary doctorate from International College (1985.)
    - Reeves, Nancy, 1987-1991 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Nancy Reeves re: Los Angeles Times letter (1987 March 4); articles in San Diego Tribune (1988 March; 1989 May 31); collected journal entries (1987 January 18-April 4.)
    - RA Miscellaneous, 1985, 1986, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      Correspondents include: Wayne Radziminski (teacher, Haddonfield Public Schools, NJ) re adaptation of "Hands Across America" project; Susan Rankaitis re request of slides of Wayne's work for ARTTALK lecture; Carter Ratcliff re essay for Tamarind catalogue; Bernadine Ratliff re gathering information on women artists employed by federal and state governments under 1930s New Deal programs; Rose L. Rashmir re book sent by Wayne.
    - Young, Joseph, 1977, 1978, 1979, 1983, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      Correspondents include: William K. McClelland (President, California Confederation of the Arts) re controversy over Young's Triforium art piece; also includes Joseph Young's biography and articles about Triforium.
    - ZE Miscellaneous, 1983, 1987, 1988, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      Correspondents include: Harriet Zeitlin (artist) to Catherine Lord (Dean, School of Art, California Institute of the Arts) re becoming a visiting artist; Los Angeles Times obituary for Jacob Zeitlin (Aug. 31, 1987); Kathy Zimmerer (Director, University Art Gallery, CSU Dominguez Hills); Anita Zengals [?]; Chloe Zerwick re Wayne's "Djuna Set" catalogue.
    - Wolfson, Ella, 1968, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      Correspondents include: Ella Wolfson re work of her husband, William Wolfson; includes exhibition brochures and invitations.
    - Wolf, Michele, ca.1970 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      Chapter outline of "Attitudes Towards Women in the Hollywood Novel," doctoral dissertation, University of Paris IV, Sorbonne; includes tables and graphs (in English and French) and sample pages.
    - Who's Who in California, 1969, 1970, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      Correspondents include: Kenneth H. Petchenik re Wayne's edited biographical information for contribution to Who's Who in California.
    - Who's Who In The United States, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      Biographical form for 1975 edition and brochure for Who's Who In the United States.
    - Pomodoro, Gio, 1968, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      Includes from Giò Pomodoro (sculptor) a postcard of Schloss Schönbrunn, Vienna; catalogue of his work, "Luogo delle misure 1977/78: scultura e materiali progettuali" (Piazza dei Signori, Verona, 1980 September.)
    - Mc Miscellaneous: McCartney, Carole; McPhail, Don; McCann, Cecile; McHugh, Jim; McQuire, Claudie., 1984, 1986, 1990, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      Correspondents include: Cecile McCann; Carole McCartney re the Los Angeles Women's Alliance for the Arts; Mavadret [?] Nelson re available materials for Esther McCoy archives; Claudie McGuire (in French); Jim McHugh; Don McPhail re receiving Wayne's book, purchasing two of Wayne's prints, and Ofelia [Garcia?] moving to Atlanta; Genevieve McSweeney.
    - Myrrh, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      Correspondents include: Trudy Myrrh Reagan re meeting Wayne; also includes issue of Ylem: Artists Using Science and Technology newsletter (vol. 11, no. 1, Feb. 1991.)
    - McWilliams, Peter, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      Correspondents include: Peter McWilliams (Prelude Press) re quoting Wayne in his book, "Ain't Nobody's Business If You Do: The Absurdity of Consensual Crimes in a Free Society."
    - AM MISCELLANEOUS: Amos, Sarah., 1992, 1993, 1994, 1995, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      Sarah Amos (Master Printer and Director of the Vermont Studio Center Press, 1994-2004) re her moving to New York to work with Bob Blackburn, moving to work as resident artist/printer at Vermont Studio Center, travels to Australia and Canada; Wayne going to New York to work with Judith Solodkin.
    - AN Miscellaneous, 1991, 1993, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      Correspondents include: Isabel Anderson re error in Art Week and meeting Wayne at Judith Hoffberg's open house; Mark W. Anderson (Professor of Art, Corpus Christi State University, TX) re Wayne's help with student's presentation; holiday card from Wallis Annenberg.
    - Aillagon, Jean-Jacques, 1982, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      Re Irène Mroz (artist) possible involvement with the Los Angeles 1984 Olympic preparations and working in the United States; exhibition announcement for "Paris-Rome-Athènes" at Ecole des Beaux-Arts, Paris (1982 May 11-July 18); Wayne's visit to Paris; Nathan Shapira re contacts at College Art Association (CAA.)
    - Kaplan, Abe, 1954, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      Examples of Abraham Kaplan's writings, including: "Referential Meaning in the Arts" (reprinted from The Journal of Aesthetics and Art Criticism, vol. XII, no. 4, 1954 June); various fables; also includes Kaplan's obituary (Los Angeles Times, 1993 June 22.)
    - Chuck Kline & Family, 1982, 1987, 1988, 1993, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      Correspondents include: Chuck [Wayne's mother's youngest brother] and Julie Klein re their new home in Polson, MO and Chuck's knee operation; Rick Klein re publishing of his art work; also includes copy of Missoulian newspaper article re Rick Klein and snowy owls; Francine Klugsman re Wayne's exhibition of "The Dorothy Series" at UCLA.
    - Barrett, Catherine, 1982, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      Re taking architecture licensing examinations, invitation to wedding of Catherine Barrett and Robert Younger, and establishment of Barrett Gleason & Associates architectural office; also includes two issues of "Arcade: The Northwest Calendar for Architecture and Design" (Vol. IV, No. 1, 1984 April/May; Vol. IV, No. 2, 1984 June/July.
    - Broadd, Dr. Harry, 1954, 1959, 1964, 1968, 1976, 1980, 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      Correspondents include: Harry A. Broadd (Professor of Art History, Northeastern Illinois University) re his manuscript, "Art of Lithography in America"; acquiring slides from check list of lithographers; article on Wayne for Our Art Heritage publication by Arts & Activities; death of Harry Broadd (1983 October 3.)
    - Bushmiller, Edgar Allen, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 15)
      Includes examples from Bushmiller's copy art and mail art projects.
    - City of Los Angeles Board of Public Works, 1985, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      Correspondents include: Bee Canterbury Lavery (Chief of Protocol, Office of the Mayor [Tom Bradley] of Los Angeles) re Wayne's attendance at ceremony honoring Marcia Wilson Hobbs (President, Greater Los Angeles Zoo Association); Maureen A. Kindel (President, Board of Public Works) re Wayne's attendance at Watts Towers/Art Center/Community Tour (1985 March 28.)
    - Avati, Mario, 1981-1983, 1985, 1987-1990, 1992-1995 (Box 21, Folder 8)